<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>World - Los Angeles Times</title>
    <link>http://www.latimes.com/world/rss2.0.xml</link>
    <description>Coverage of the top world news stories from across the globe, including politics, breaking news and opinion.</description>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>&#xA9;2017 Los Angeles Times</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 07:26:39 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
    <title>North Korea&apos;s missile launch is a triumph for the rogue nation, &apos;worrisome&apos; for the world</title>
	<dc:creator>Matt Stiles</dc:creator>
	<link>http://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-north-korea-nuclear-missile-20171129-story.html</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
	  <p>For more than two months, North Korea refrained from public displays of its nuclear and ballistic missile technology, offering guarded hope that the communist nation had paused its ambitions — at least for a bit.</p> <p>Such optimism disappeared on Wednesday when United States and South Korean military...</p>
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 07:10:00 PST</pubDate>
<media:thumbnail url="http://www.trbimg.com/img-5a1ecf6c/turbine/la-fg-north-korea-nuclear-missile-20171129/600"/>
      </item>
<item>
    <title>Honduras still hasn&apos;t declared a winner in its presidential vote — and tensions are rising</title>
	<dc:creator>Kate Linthicum</dc:creator>
	<link>http://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-honduras-election-20171128-story.html</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
	  <p>Protesters from opposing political parties took to the streets Tuesday in Honduras, where election officials still have not declared a winner in Sunday’s presidential vote amid allegations of fraud.</p> <p>International monitors called for a speedier and more transparent vote count as several prominent...</p>
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 17:55:00 PST</pubDate>
<media:thumbnail url="http://www.trbimg.com/img-5a1e2cc9/turbine/la-fg-honduras-election-20171128/600"/>
      </item>
<item>
    <title>Could a North Korean missile hit Washington? Latest ICBM launch suggests it&apos;s possible</title>
	<dc:creator>Matt Stiles</dc:creator>
	<link>http://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-north-korea-missile-20171128-story.html</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
	  <p>North Korea on Wednesday test-launched a ballistic missile for the first time since September, its latest provocation that could further exacerbate tensions with the international community.</p> <p>The launch occurred at 3:17 a.m. from Pyongsong, in South Pyongan province, and the missile flew into the...</p>
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 16:25:00 PST</pubDate>
<media:thumbnail url="http://www.trbimg.com/img-5a1e262a/turbine/la-fg-north-korea-missile-20171128/600"/>
      </item>
<item>
    <title>China sentences Taiwanese man to 5 years in prison for advocating democracy</title>
	<dc:creator>Ralph Jennings</dc:creator>
	<link>http://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-taiwan-china-sentence-20171128-story.html</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
	  <p>A court in China sentenced a man from Taiwan to five years in prison Tuesday over his advocacy of democracy, a verdict that could drive the rival governments further apart instead of nudging them toward Beijing’s eventual goal of unification.</p> <p>A court in southern city of Yueyang convicted Lee Ming-che,...</p>
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 16:15:00 PST</pubDate>
<media:thumbnail url="http://www.trbimg.com/img-5a1dfd2a/turbine/la-fg-taiwan-china-sentence-20171128/600"/>
      </item>
<item>
    <title>In unusual criticism, Tillerson slams Russia&apos;s &apos;malicious tactics&apos; ahead of trip to Europe</title>
	<dc:creator>Tracy Wilkinson</dc:creator>
	<link>http://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-tillerson-russia-20171128-story.html</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
	  <p>In some of the toughest criticism of Russia to come out of the Trump administration, Secretary of State Rex Tillerson slammed Moscow on Tuesday for what he called a campaign of force, intimidation and subterfuge in an attempt to overpower neighbors and reassert a position of dominance on the world...</p>
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 13:45:00 PST</pubDate>
<media:thumbnail url="http://www.trbimg.com/img-5a1dd9a5/turbine/la-fg-tillerson-russia-20171128/600"/>
      </item>
<item>
    <title>Syrian government delegation to join U.N.-sponsored talks a day late</title>
	<dc:creator>Alexandra Zavis</dc:creator>
	<link>http://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-syria-talks-20171128-story.html</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
	  <p>An eighth round of United Nations-sponsored talks aimed at finding a solution to Syria’s ruinous civil war got under way in Geneva on Tuesday without the participation of representatives from the Syrian government, a sign of their displeasure at the continuing insistence of opposition negotiators...</p>
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 12:15:00 PST</pubDate>
<media:thumbnail url="http://www.trbimg.com/img-5a1e022a/turbine/la-fg-syria-talks-20171128/600"/>
      </item>
<item>
    <title>Hillary Clinton, taking a different tone than Trump, hits China on human rights and South China Sea</title>
	<dc:creator>Jessica Meyers</dc:creator>
	<link>http://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-china-hillary-20171128-story.html</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
	  <p>Hillary Clinton spoke to the Chinese audience as if she were giving a presidential address.</p> <p>The former White House contender delivered a pointed, forceful attack Tuesday aimed at President Trump and Chinese President Xi Jinping, with whom the U.S. leader claims a unique chemistry. Her remarks —...</p>
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 07:55:00 PST</pubDate>
<media:thumbnail url="http://www.trbimg.com/img-5a1d8b35/turbine/la-fg-china-hillary-20171128/600"/>
      </item>
<item>
    <title>It&apos;s nearly Prince Harry&apos;s turn, along with fiancee Meghan Markle, to join Britain&apos;s royal history of matrimony</title>
	<dc:creator>Christina Boyle</dc:creator>
	<link>http://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-britain-harry-meghan-20171127-story.html</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
	  <p>Meghan Markle is many things: an American, a divorcee, a television actress, the daughter of an African-American mother and white father of Dutch-Irish descent, a Catholic and a 36-year-old, which makes her three years older than her fiance, Prince Harry.</p> <p>All of those identities will make her one...</p>
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 03:00:00 PST</pubDate>
<media:thumbnail url="http://www.trbimg.com/img-5a1ce92d/turbine/la-fg-britain-harry-meghan-20171127/600"/>
      </item>
<item>
    <title>Little optimism as new round of Syria peace talks set to open</title>
	<dc:creator>Laura King</dc:creator>
	<link>http://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-syria-talks-20171127-story.html</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
	  <p>It doesn’t usually bode well for peace talks when the attendance of one of the principals is still up in the air on the eve of the gathering.</p> <p>An eighth round of United Nations-backed talks aimed at finding a political solution to Syria’s grinding civil war was to convene Tuesday in Geneva, but...</p>
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 15:45:00 PST</pubDate>
<media:thumbnail url="http://www.trbimg.com/img-5a1cae3e/turbine/la-fg-syria-talks-20171127/600"/>
      </item>
<item>
    <title>South Korea&apos;s loudspeakers blast North Korea with word of defecting soldier&apos;s ill health</title>
	<dc:creator>Matt Stiles</dc:creator>
	<link>http://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-south-korea-loudspeaker-20171127-story.html</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
	  <p>South Korea’s high-decibel loudspeakers on the border with longtime foe North Korea have at times blasted messages intended to inform, agitate, or taunt people on the other side.</p> <p>The nation’s latest blaring border announcement says that one of communist North Korea’s soldiers defected two weeks...</p>
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 12:55:00 PST</pubDate>
<media:thumbnail url="http://www.trbimg.com/img-5a1cb427/turbine/la-fg-south-korea-loudspeaker-20171127/600"/>
      </item>
<item>
    <title>Central Asian migrants caught in Turkey&apos;s anti-terror raids</title>
	<dc:creator>Umar Farooq</dc:creator>
	<link>http://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-turkey-central-asians-20171125-story.html</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
	  <p>The last time Anurkhol Bipolotov saw her husband, Fakhriddin, was across a street, outside a police station in Istanbul, on March 9.</p> <p>“He couldn’t speak, and I asked to speak with him, but they shouted, ‘You cannot speak.’ Then they sent him to Uzbekistan,” she recalled. “Now I have no idea where...</p>
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 03:00:00 PST</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
    <title>&apos;I am their family.&apos; In Tunisia, one man&apos;s mission to bury the migrants who die at sea</title>
	<dc:creator>Molly Hennessy-Fiske</dc:creator>
	<link>http://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-tunisia-migrant-cemetery-20171126-story.html</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
	  <p>Despite his injured ankle, he ran as best he could in his rubber boots to reach the graves.</p> <p>Chamseddine Marzoug was in a hurry, taking advantage of a break in torrential rains to check the swelling cemetery he has spent the last dozen years building for hundreds of African migrants who never made...</p>
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 03:00:00 PST</pubDate>
<media:thumbnail url="http://www.trbimg.com/img-5a1db0aa/turbine/la-fg-tunisia-migrant-cemetery-20171126/600"/>
      </item>
<item>
    <title>Rep. John Conyers quits House committee post amid sexual harassment probe</title>
	<dc:creator>Tracy Wilkinson</dc:creator>
	<link>http://www.latimes.com/world/la-na-pol-sexual-misconduct-politics-20171126-story.html</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
	  <p>Sexual abuse allegations continued to roil U.S. politics Sunday, with Democratic Rep. John Conyers Jr. stepping down from a powerful House post and President Trump again voicing support for Republican Alabama Senate candidate Roy Moore.</p> <p>Conyers announced he was stepping down as ranking member of...</p>
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 14:20:00 PST</pubDate>
<media:thumbnail url="http://www.trbimg.com/img-5a1b69d1/turbine/la-na-pol-sexual-misconduct-politics-20171126/600"/>
      </item>
<item>
    <title>&apos;They were shooting anyone who seemed to be breathing.&apos; Survivors recount the horror of Egypt mosque attack</title>
	<dc:creator>Omar Medhat, Alexandra Zavis</dc:creator>
	<link>http://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-egypt-mosque-aftermath-20171125-story.html</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
	  <p>The assailants arrived in five all-terrain vehicles: between 25 and 30 gunmen clad in military-style camouflage pants and black T-shirts and carrying an Islamic State flag.</p> <p>They positioned themselves at the main gate of a Sufi mosque and in its 12 windows. Then, as the imam was about to deliver...</p>
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2017 17:00:00 PST</pubDate>
<media:thumbnail url="http://www.trbimg.com/img-5a1a238f/turbine/la-fg-egypt-mosque-aftermath-20171125/600"/>
      </item>
<item>
    <title>Who are Sufi Muslims and why are they the target of Muslim extremists?</title>
	<dc:creator>Nabih Bulos</dc:creator>
	<link>http://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-egypt-sufi-muslims-20171125-story.html</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
	  <p>When some two dozen militants massacred at least 305 people in the Sinai Peninsula on Friday, they were targeting the Sufi community that worshiped in the area’s Rawda mosque.</p> <p>Even though no group has claimed responsibility, Egyptian state news agency MENA said the attack “appeared” to have been...</p>
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2017 16:25:00 PST</pubDate>
<media:thumbnail url="http://www.trbimg.com/img-5a1a0abf/turbine/la-fg-egypt-sufi-muslims-20171125/600"/>
      </item>
<item>
    <title>Pakistan deploys army in capital after deadly police clash with supporters of radical cleric</title>
	<dc:creator>Aoun Sahi</dc:creator>
	<link>http://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-pakistan-clashes-20171125-story.html</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
	  <p>Pakistani anti-riot police and paramilitary forces fired tear gas and rubber bullets Saturday to disperse thousands of supporters of a radical cleric who had blocked a key road into the capital for two weeks.</p> <p>Five people were killed and more than 200 injured in the clashes, hospital officials said,...</p>
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2017 09:20:00 PST</pubDate>
<media:thumbnail url="http://www.trbimg.com/img-5a1a006e/turbine/la-fg-pakistan-clashes-20171125/600"/>
      </item>
<item>
    <title>In first papal visit to Myanmar, Pope Francis faces a dilemma: whether to say &apos;Rohingya&apos;</title>
	<dc:creator>Shashank Bengali</dc:creator>
	<link>http://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-myanmar-pope-francis-20171125-story.html</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
	  <p>In August, responding to the first reports of Rohingya Muslims fleeing an army-led crackdown in Myanmar, Pope Francis called on his flock to pray for “our Rohingya brethren.”</p> <p>“Let all of us ask the Lord to save them, and to raise up men and women of goodwill to help them, who shall give them their...</p>
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2017 03:00:00 PST</pubDate>
<media:thumbnail url="http://www.trbimg.com/img-5a198cc6/turbine/la-fg-myanmar-pope-francis-20171125-thumbnail/600"/>
      </item>
<item>
    <title>An awkward partnership might be the solution to Germany&apos;s political stalemate</title>
	<dc:creator>Erik Kirschbaum</dc:creator>
	<link>http://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-germany-merkel-government-20171124-story.html</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
	  <p>After an inconclusive fall election threatened to paralyze Germany’s leadership, the renewal of an uncomfortable right-left partnership could herald an end to what analysts had been calling the country’s worst post-war political crisis.</p> <p>The center-left Social Democrats abruptly said Friday that...</p>
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 17:40:00 PST</pubDate>
<media:thumbnail url="http://www.trbimg.com/img-5a1a32ba/turbine/la-fg-germany-merkel-government-20171124/600"/>
      </item>
<item>
    <title>At least 235 killed in Egypt as militants attack Sinai mosque</title>
	<dc:creator>Omar Medhat, Nabih Bulos, Alexandra Zavis</dc:creator>
	<link>http://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-egypt-mosque-20171124-story.html</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
	  <p>At least 235 people were killed when gunmen stormed a mosque during Friday prayers in the rugged Sinai Peninsula, setting off explosives and firing on worshipers in what was believed to be the deadliest single attack by Islamist extremists on Egyptian civilians.</p> <p>There was no immediate claim of...</p>
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 14:15:00 PST</pubDate>
<media:thumbnail url="http://www.trbimg.com/img-5a18cc57/turbine/la-fg-egypt-mosque-20171124/600"/>
      </item>
<item>
    <title>On the shadowlands of the frontier, a U.S. border agent plans his future in Mexico</title>
	<dc:creator>Lauren Villagran</dc:creator>
	<link>http://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-border-patrol-agent-2017-htmlstory.html</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
	  More than half of U.S. Border Patrol agents are Latinos, and many have closer ties to Mexico than to the United States. Ramiro Cordero spends his days patrolling the El Paso sector, and his nights dreaming of the day he'll retire in Mexico.
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 13:55:00 PST</pubDate>
<media:thumbnail url="http://www.trbimg.com/img-5a18c46f/turbine/la-fg-border-patrol-agent-2017/600"/>
      </item>
<item>
    <title>Many in China outraged by shocking sexual abuse allegations at a kindergarten in Beijing</title>
	<dc:creator>Jonathan Kaiman</dc:creator>
	<link>http://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-china-kindergarten-abuse-20171124-story.html</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
	  <p>Several parents have accused a Beijing kindergarten of drugging and sexually abusing their children, causing an upswell of anger on Chinese social media and prompting an investigation into abuse at kindergartens nationwide.</p> <p>Children at a school run by the Beijing-based, New York-listed RYB Education...</p>
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 07:30:00 PST</pubDate>
<media:thumbnail url="http://www.trbimg.com/img-5a18ee71/turbine/la-fg-china-kindergarten-abuse-20171124/600"/>
      </item>
<item>
    <title>Colombian coca farmers, facing a threat to their livelihood, resist U.S.-backed efforts to eradicate cocaine production</title>
	<dc:creator>Chris Kraul</dc:creator>
	<link>http://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-colombia-cocaine-2017-htmlstory.html</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
	  Colombian farmers resist U.S.-backed efforts to eradicate cocaine production
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2017 03:00:00 PST</pubDate>
<media:thumbnail url="http://www.trbimg.com/img-5a175a0b/turbine/la-fg-colombia-cocaine-2017/600"/>
      </item>
<item>
    <title>Argentina says missing submarine suffered explosion but doesn&apos;t know the crew&apos;s fate</title>
	<dc:creator>Andres D&amp;apos;Alessandro, Chris Kraul</dc:creator>
	<link>http://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-argentina-missing-submarine-20171123-story.html</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
	  <p>An international flotilla of ships and several high-tech aircraft searching for a missing Argentine submarine focused on an area in the southern Atlantic Ocean on Thursday after authorities confirmed acoustical evidence of an explosion coming from the lost vessel with 44 crew members aboard.</p> <p>The...</p>
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 16:45:00 PST</pubDate>
<media:thumbnail url="http://www.trbimg.com/img-5a17801b/turbine/la-fg-argentina-missing-submarine-20171123/600"/>
      </item>
<item>
    <title>What we know and don&apos;t know about Argentina&apos;s missing submarine</title>
	<dc:creator>Andres D&amp;apos;Alessandro and Chris Kraul</dc:creator>
	<link>http://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-argentina-missing-submarine-20171122-story.html</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
	  <p>A full week after the Argentine submarine’s disappearance, there was no news Wednesday, encouraging or otherwise, about the whereabouts of the San Juan and its 44 crew members. The diesel-electric powered sub disappeared Nov. 15 as it cruised northward from the southern port of Ushuaia toward the...</p>
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 20:00:00 PST</pubDate>
<media:thumbnail url="http://www.trbimg.com/img-5a16f6e0/turbine/la-fg-argentina-missing-submarine-20171122/600"/>
      </item>
<item>
    <title>U.S. declares military campaign in Myanmar to be ethnic cleansing</title>
	<dc:creator>Tracy Wilkinson</dc:creator>
	<link>http://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-tillerson-ethnic-cleansing-20171122-story.html</link>
	<description><![CDATA[
	  <p>The United States on Wednesday joined other world powers and declared that the brutal campaign against Muslims in Myanmar amounts to ethnic cleansing.</p> <p>Secretary of State Rex Tillerson said the <a href="http://www.latimes.com/world/asia/la-fg-asean-rohingya-2017-htmlstory.html" target="_blank">ongoing violence</a> that has claimed the lives of thousands of Rohingya Muslims and driven many more from...</p>
	]]></description>
	<pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 16:30:00 PST</pubDate>
<media:thumbnail url="http://www.trbimg.com/img-5a162854/turbine/la-fg-tillerson-ethnic-cleansing-20171122/600"/>
      </item>
</channel> 
</rss>
